Guide to the Leon F. Litwack Collection of Berkeley, California, Protest Literature
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Leon F. Litwack collection of Berkeley, California, protest literature
1939-2004
1964-1989
WA MSS S-2616
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
12
(15 boxes)
The collection consists of newspapers, periodicals, flyers, handbills, newsletters, mailings, memoranda, reports, sound recordings, and other materials compiled by Leon Litwack that primarily document the protest movements of the 1960s and 1970s, particularly in and around Berkeley, California. The collection includes materials related to civil rights, Vietnam War protests, the Black Panther Party, the Free Speech Movement and the counterculture of the 1960s and 1970s. Also included are memoranda, meeting minutes, reports, and publications distributed to faculty at the University of California, Berkeley.
Litwack, Leon F.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Serendipity Books on the Frederick W. and Carrie S. Beinecke Fund for Western Americana, 2008.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Associated Materials
Other printed material received with the collection was removed for separate cataloging and can be accessed by searching Orbis (Yale's Online Catalog).
Leon F. Litwack
Leon F. Litwack was born in 1929 in Santa Barbara, California. He received a B.A. (1951) and Ph.D. (1958) from the University of California at Berkeley, where he also served as a professor in the History Department from 1965 to 2007. Litwack's scholarship focused on African-American history and he won the Pulitzer Prize in 1980 for his book, Been in the Storm So Long: The Aftermath of Slavery.
Scope and Contents
The Leon F. Litwack Collection of Berkeley, California, Protest Literature consists of newspapers, periodicals, flyers, handbills, newsletters, mailings, memoranda, reports, sound recordings, and other materials compiled by Leon Litwack that primarily document the protest movements of the 1960s and 1970s, particularly in and around Berkeley, California. The collection includes materials related to civil rights, Vietnam War protests, the Black Panther Party, the Free Speech Movement and the counterculture of the 1960s and 1970s. Also included are memoranda, meeting minutes, reports, and publications distributed to faculty at the University of California, Berkeley.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into four series: I. Files. II. Newspapers. III. Periodicals. IV. Sound Recordings.
Berkeley barb; Daily Californian (Berkeley, Calif.); Civil rights -- California -- Berkeley -- 20th Century; Counterculture -- California -- Berkeley -- 20th Century; Freedom of speech -- California -- Berkeley -- 20th Century; Protest literature -- California -- Berkeley -- 20th Century; Vietnam War, 1961-1975 -- Protest movements -- California -- Berkeley; Fliers (printed matter); Handbills; Memorandums; Newsletters; Newspapers; Periodicals; Reports; Sound recordings; Litwack, Leon F.; Black Panther Party; University of California, Berkeley
- Files, Series I; 4; (4 boxes)
  Arrangement
  The files and the material within them have been kept in the order in which they were received by the library. The original file folders have been replaced and some of the original "files" now occupy multiple folders.
  General note
  The alphabetical item list for each file is based on a list prepared by the staff of Serendipity Books in Berkelely, California, which accompanied the collection. Library staff has not verified the contents of each folder against the list, nor does the list reflect the physical order of material within any file. There is no item list for File 13.
  - File 1 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    The item list does not reflect the physical organization of items within the file.
    - A TIME TO GROOVE AND A TIME TO DISOBEY
    - ACADEMIC PUBLICITY FUND
    - Adler (Nathan), School of Criminology, et al..Dear Colleague. Jan 26, 1971.
    - AUG. 6th-9th / DAYS OF PROTESTmore than 40 groups will join to protest war in Vietnam in SF
    - BATTLE OF BERKELEY-BACKGROUND.
    - Berkeley Community for McCarthy (org). EUGENE McCARTHY / He Was There
    - Black Panther Party for Self-Defense. WHAT WE WANT / WHAT WE BELIEVE
    - Blackmens Draft Counselling Alliance, SF. (org). DID YOU KNOW (six of ten soldiers in Vietnam are black)
    - BOB SCHEER WILL SPEAK
    - Campus Coordinating Committee, University of California, Berkeley. NOON RALLY.
    - Campus Friends of AFT Local 1570 (org). TEN DAYS TO SHAKE UP THE UNIVERSITY
    - Campus Peace and Freedom (org). CONTROL THE COPS, DEFEND FREE SPEECH.
    - Campus Peace and Freedom (org). FREE HUEY RALLY! Sunday July 28. Cleaver, Seale, Carmichael, Tijerina, Ivan Dixon, Mike Klonsky all spoke.
    - Campus Peace and Freedom Movement. WHY WONT McCARTHY
    - Campus SDS (org). UNCLE SAM STILL WANTS YOU.
    - Campus SDS (org). WE CAN WIN!
    - Campus SDS. SUPPORT YANK-FIGHT REPRESSION. June 6, 1969.
    - Citizens for Creative Social Change (org). DR. JOEL FORT LEGAL SUPPORT FUND, 4pp.
    - CLARIFICATION. Free Speech Movement vs University of California, Berkeley.
    - Claude For Congress Committee (org). FOR THE EAST BAY / CLAUDE HURCHISON / Leadership / US Congress
    - Cleaveland (Brad) graduate student. $20 MILLIONposition paper, 8pp.
    - Committee on Academic Freedom, University of California, Berkeley (org). PROPOSITIONS INTRODUCED.
    - Community for New Politics (org). COMMUNITY FOR NEW POLITICS (Scheer Campaign)
    - Community for New Politics. CONFRONT THE POLICE HARASSMENT ISSUE. Pink paper
    - COPS ON CAMPUS / STRIKE! Docket: Handed out on Sproul Plaza / Thursday morning.
    - CPE (org). DEAR FACULTY.
    - Dick Gregory for President Committee (org). DICK GREGORY PEACE FEAST
    - END RACISM / Michael Jones For Supervisor, 4th District, Alameda CountyFree Huey Newton. 4pp.
    - ETHEL & JULIUS ROSENBERG / Executed for a Crime, 8pp. With envelope, Bay Area Committee to Re-Open the Rosenberg Case.
    - FACULTY (University of California, Berkeley) FOR MCCARTHY
    - FOR THE CITY COUNCIL (of Berkeley) Elect RONALD V. DELLUMS and Re-Elect BERNICE HUBBARD MAY
    - Free Speech Movement Newsletter, 4pp. [late 1964]
    - Free Speech Movement WE WANT A UNIVERSITY, 7 leaves
    - Free Speech Movement. Free Speech Movement ACTION
    - Free Speech Movement. PROVISIONAL PLATFORM. Yellow paper.
    - FREE STUDENT UNION ORIENTATION.
    - FREE UNIVERSITY OF BERKELEY / COUNTER CURRICULUM PROJECT
    - Freuhan (George J.) senior, UCB. SOLUTION OR DIVERSION? Duplicate but docketed handed out at entry to Ac. Sen. Meeting Mon 5 Dec.
    - Free Speech Movement ACTION
    - Free Speech Movement. WHY ARE UC STUDENTS STILL NOT SATISFIED?
    - Group of Faculty, University of California, Berkeley. STATEMENT TO THE CITIZENS OF CALIFORNIA
    - Ham (Roswell G.) class of 1914. OPEN LETTER TO THE STUDENTS AND FACULTY OF THE UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, 4pp.
    - HEAR ABOUT THE LAOTIAN LIBERATION STRUGGLE. / 3 Speakers. Sunday, April 5. On verso: STEVE CANYON IN LAOS by Gar Smith, 1970 = comic strip [adapted!?] in color. One edge torn (no loss).
    - Heyn (Chancellor) A STATEMENT, 1p.
    - Independent Socialist Club (org) RUBIN FOR MAYOR. White paper
    - Independent Socialist Club (org) RUBIN FOR MAYOR. Yellow paper
    - Independent Socialist Club (org). DEFEND THE GHETTO UPRISINGS, 4pp.
    - Independent Socialist Club (org). NO CONFIDENCE. Docketed handed out at entry to Ac. Sen. Meet / Mon 5 Dec. Cartoon verso by Lisa Lyons.
    - International Days of Protest Peace Marech Committee (org). WE MARCH IN MOURNING. Illustrated poster.
    - JAZZ CONCERT /Free Speech Movement and SLATE
    - JEREMIAH STAMLER, MD Legal Aid Fund. Contribution solicitation. Blue paper.
    - JOIN LA RAZA TO DELANO
    - KEEP HOPE ALIVEVoter Registration Rally.Rev. JESSE JACKSON. (pink paper)
    - Kennedy (Robert F.) DINNER PARTY, Friday Aug 4, Fairmont Hotel, SF. RFK spoke. Blue paper.
    - MALCOLM X postcard 1999, mailed 2000, with image & addresses
    - MARCH FOR McCARTHY July 27
    - McKenzie (John) / ASUC Senate DEAR FACULTY MEMBER
    - Meerpols. Finance the Meerpols lawsuit, contribution slip
    - MICHAEL JONES WANTS TO REPRESENT YOU (black cabdidate, 29 year old Air Force vet. 4pp.
    - NOON RALLY BULLETIN. Tues Oct 17. Stop the Draft Week
    - OPEN LETTER (unsigned) to Regents, University of California, Berkeley. [Advocates REJECTION OF PROPOSAL OF ACADEMIC SENATE, Dec 8, 1964]
    - OPEN LETTER TO FACULTY MEMBERS OF THE UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA AT BERKELEY. Yellow paper
    - OUR FUNCTION IS TO ACT AS NEUTRAL OBSERVERS (faded faculty statement)
    - Peace and Freedom Movement. SCHEER FOR CONGRESS
    - Peace and Freedom Movement. ELECT THE HEAD, YELLEADER/SOKOL
    - PEOPLES PARK. Photo essay, printed blue wrs, 12pp. Signed Sam Shore. Berkeley.
    - PEOPLES MEDICAL HANDBOOK, 12pp. Berkeley: Christian Revolutionary Medical Committees.
    - Poinsett (Alex) THIRTEEN YEARS AFTER 1954. Offprint, Ebony, April 1967.
    - Progressive Labor Party Student Club (University of California, Berkeley) (org). NO VIRTUE IN SILENCE.
    - PROTEST HUAC WITCHHUNT(multi-sponsored)
    - QUAKERS SPONSOR UNIQUE PLAN
    - RADICAL CAUCUS. Sunday, Dec 29
    - Resistance (The) (org). THE RESISTANCE PROUDLY PRESENTSEye Witness: North Vietnam
    - RESOLUTION TO BE SUBMITTED TO THE AHA BUSINESS MEETING BY THE RADICAL HISTORIANS CAUCUS
    - SCAL / Slate (org). PICKET CDC CONVENTION
    - SENATOR EUGENE McCARTHY FOR PRESIDENT
    - SENATOR EUGENE McCARTHY FOR PRESIDENT
    - SPEAKER FROM DELANO (on UC campus)
    - SPONSORS (partial list) / JEREMIAH STAMLER, MD / Legal Aid Fund, 4pp.
    - Students and other progressives for Robert F. Kennedy (org). KENNEDY, McCARTHY
    - SUPPORT OUR TROOPS IN LAOS (illus)
    - TEXT OF STATEMENT (coupon clipped)
    - THE FACULTY SPEAKS OUT BOLDLY / handout on Plaza Tues AM Dec 6
    - THREE SOLDIERS REFUSE TO FIGHT Friday July 8
    - TO OUR COUSINS IN THE ARMY / verso: TO OUR BROTHERS
    - University of California, Berkeley (Academic Senate?) [RESOLUTIONor CALL in two sections], docketed, did not reach floor
    - University of California, Berkeley Academic Senate. RESOLUTION APPROVED..
    - University of California, Berkeley campus W.E.B. DuBois Club (org). THE SIGNIFICANCE OF THE BLACK POWER CONFERENCE.
    - UNIVERSITY PROFESSORS AGAINST UNITED STATES AGRESSION IN VIETNAM. Week of Oct 16-21
    - University Society of Libertarians (org). PRINCIPLES.
    - University Students for Law and Order (org). Executive Committee. WHAT HAS THE Free Speech Movement ACCOMPLISHED?
    - Vietnam Day Committee (org). COMMUNITY ACTION COMMITTEEOctober 15-16. Orange paper.
    - Vietnam Day Committee (org). PLEASE GIVE US YOUR NAME.
    - VOTE BALABANIAN FOR CONGRESS
    - VOTE SOCIALIST / Peter Camejo / SWP Senatorial Candidate
    - WANTED FOR NOTHING LESS THAN ASUC SENATORCARL WALSH (illustrated)LIBERAL REWARD. Yellow paper.
    - West Coast Committee for Democracy in Greece (org). DEAR FRIEND OF GREECE.
    - WHAT HAPPENEDSTRIKE! Docket: handed out on Sproul Plaza Thursday Morning
    - YPSL, Norman Thomas Chapter (org). ARE YOU ABOUT TO ENGAGE IN AN ACT / with Feiffer drawing. Pink paper.
    - YPSL, Norman Thomas Chapter, University of California, Berkeley. PACIFISM AND ANARCHISM.
  - File 2 (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
    - Alameda County Peace & Freedom Movement/ ANNOUNCEMENTS (defective)
    - Alameda County Platform Committee, Peace and Freedom Party.
    - APRIL COALITION PLATFORM. Jan 15-19
    - Auther (Barbara L.) PROPOSED PLATFORM FOR PEACE AND FREEDOM PARTY, 4pp.
    - Bay Area Revolutionary Union (org). EXTEND THE ANTI IMPER. STRUGGLE
    - Berkeley Coalition CAMBODIA: The Price of Expedient Liberalism. Signed by Dellums
    - Berkeley Coalition. COHELANS LIBERALISM. Signed in print by Ron Dellums
    - Berkeley Community for McCarthy (org)
    - BIOGRAPHICAL BACKGROUND ON MICHAEL JONES.
    - Black Panther Party (org). NOTES ON THE BLACK PANTHER PATY, 3pp.
    - Boy Scouts of America / Freedoms Foundation, Inc. Bell-shaped Vote encourager
    - BOYCOTT $AFEWAY!
    - Campus Friends of SNCC (or) SUPPORT THE BLACK PANTHERS.
    - Campus Peace and Freedom Movement (org). WHY WONT McCARTHY
    - Campus Young Socialists (org) SOLIDARITY (Peter Camejo, et al)
    - Campus YSA (org). PROTEST OUTLAWING OF FRENCH STUDENT MOVEMENT STREET RALLY TONIGHT
    - CANYON PERPETUAL MOTION MACHINE July 16 Dance Picnic BENEFIT
    - Coalition for Peace and Life in El Salvador (org). DUARTE NOT COMING
    - Committee Against the Israeli Invasion of Lebanon (org) FACT SHEET ON THE ISRAELI OCCUPATION OF SOUTHERN LEBANON.
    - COMMITTEE OF RESPONSIBILITY open letter
    - Country Joe & the Fish FISH GAME (with 18 blue counters). Very fine piece.
    - CRY FOR HELP / CALL FOR UNITY. Pink paper
    - Delacour (Mike), et al. MOTIVATION:
    - DICK GREGORY FOR PRESIDENTPEACE & FREEDOM PARTY CANDIDATE
    - ECOLOGY WORKSHOP ORHANIZING PRINCIPLES
    - ECONOMIC WORKSHOP MINORITY REPORT
    - FACULTY FOR McCARTHY
    - Faculty of History Department (University of California, Berkeley) [Statement].
    - Faculty-Student Peace Comm(org). Reconstitution is not a blue-print = [first line]
    - Field Studies Program / The Wright Institute (org). DEAR FACULTY MEMBER
    - FREE SPEECH IN JEOPARDY. Free Speech Movement.
    - FREE STUDENT UNION button ballot
    - Free Speech Movement (org). STATEMENTFree Speech Movement STEERING COMMITTEE & GCC Exec Comm
    - GENERAL MEETING OF THEW HISTORY COMMUNITY
    - GOD MAY I OUTLIVE STANDARD OIL = ISSUE I [?] green cross/circle at top
    - Graubard (Phoebe) IN DEFENSE OF A COALITION BETWEEN THE PEACE & FREEDOM MOVEMENT AND THE BLACK PANTHER PARTY FOR SELF DEFENSE.
    - Hastings Street Opera RESISTANCE Benefit.
    - HUGH R. MANES / Biographical Sketch
    - IF YOU CANT GO TO NEW HAVEN. May Day for Bobby [Seale].
    - IF YOU DECIDE TO CONTINUE CLASSES
    - Independent Social. Club (org). FORUM / RECENT EVENTS IN POLAND. UC campus
    - INFORMATION SHEET FOR RESEARCH ON REPRESSION IN BERKELEY. 8pp.
    - INTERNATIONAL WOMENS DAY / dedicated to Ericka Huggins and Angela Davis
    - Israel (Barbara) & Savio (Mario) ARGUMENTS AGAINST PASSINGMOTION
    - ISSUE II / PEACE & FREEDOM. Mar 6 green cross
    - Jackson (Jesse L.) Half-tone photo, 5 x 4
    - Jackson (Jesse) Open Letter, 4pp. 1988
    - JOIN THE UNION. 4/65
    - KFRC FANTASY FAIR, 4pp.
    - Lew, de la Rosa, Cambell, Kato, signatories. Last page of an incomplete document sent to administrators at University of California, Berkeley, etc. Representing Students Against Intervention in El Salvador, student advocate; Academic Affairs Vice-President.
    - LIST OF HOTELS (2 leaves, 3pp)
    - LOADING ZONE Family Happening. Peace & Happiness in Berkeley
    - Los Angeles County PRECONVENTION MINORITY, LIBERATION WORKSHOP
    - McCarthy For President Campaign (org) IF YOU CANT MARCH FOR McCARTHY
    - McGovern (George) as US Senator. Open letter, 6 leaves
    - McGovern Million Member Club contribution receipt
    - Meher Baba League News (4pp)
    - MINORITY LIBERATION WORKSHOP / March 9 & 10 / UCLA
    - MINORITY REPORT OF THE MILITARY WORKSHOP. By Caughlan & Rutland
    - MINORITY REPORT, ELECTORAL CAMPAIGNS WORKSHOP
    - NEGRO JEWISH RELATIONS
    - Northern Calif PFMMARIJUANA, 8pp.
    - NOW IS THE TIME TO FIGHT THE KLAN.
    - PARTIES: for politics & money.
    - PAUL JACOBS FOR US SENATE
    - Peace & Freedom Movement [Party]: MEMO TO COUNTY DELEGATIONS.
    - Peace & Freedom Movement [Party]: STATE OFFICE MEMO [Peace & Freedom Party convention suggestions, etc]
    - Peace & Freedom Movement. WHATS HAPPENING? / Free picnic
    - PEACE & FREEDOM PARTY ARRANGEMENTS COMMITTEE
    - Peace and Freedom Movement (org). Alameda County Steering Committee. KING IS DEAD.
    - Peace and Freedom Movement (org). Alameda County Steering Committee. MARTIN LUTHER KING. Martin Luther King is dead. Differs slightly from other in terms of titling, formatting.
    - Peace and Freedom Party (org). CONVENTION / CALL FOR AN OPEN SENATORIAL PRIMARY.
    - PEACE AND FREEDOM SONGS / Courtesy San Diego delegation
    - POLICY STATEMENTWOMENS WORKSHOP. By Joan Roos.
    - POSITION PAPER ON COALITIONS
    - RALLY TODAY / FREEDOM SINGERS (title faded away). Flyer, University of California, Berkeley.
    - Republican National Committee / Spiro T. Agnew Speaks Out
    - RON DELLUMS FOR CONGRESS, 4pp.
    - Roos (Joan) THE RIGHTS OF WOMEN
    - Savio (Mario) REVOLUTION? MARIO SAVIO SAYS: (4pp.)
    - SDS (org). FREE LOS SIETE / DEFEND THE MOVEMENT.
    - SENATE PROBES ARMY GRAPE ORGY
    - SHOW CONGRESS OUR SUPPORT
    - SOME OF THE ACTIONS TAKEN BY THE FACULTY
    - STANLEY GOW FOR US SENATOR
    - STATEMENT, COMMITTEE ON FOREIGN POLICY, 2 leaves
    - Steering Committee, County Council, Peace & Freedom Movement. (org) 10 POINT PROGRAM OF THE BLACK PANTHER PARTY FOR SELF-DEFENSE.
    - Student Committee on Agricultural Labor (org). HELP BOYCOTT S & W.
    - Teamsters, locals 70, 298, 296, 315, 893. 896. FOR CONSUMERS..WE PROTEST
    - THE HISTORY COMMUNITY IS ON STRIKE.
    - THE LIBERALS SONG
    - TORCH BTU
    - UNIVERSITY REFORM MOVEMENT.
    - University Young Republicans (org). RIGHT MEETS LEFT
    - VOICE PLATFORM.
    - WE DEMAND A STATEMENT OF PINCIPLES
    - Wisconsin Socialist Club (org). TO ABOLISH THE UN-AMERICAN ACTIVITIES COMMITTEE.. Large folded broadsheet printed on two sides attached
    - WL SALVADOR UPDATE: Duarte Regime in Crisis
    - WORKSHOP PROPOSALSC. P. Herrick
    - Young Peoples Social. League (org). 3rd Annual SOCIALIST CAMP. Aug 18 ff
  - File 3 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - BOARD OF SUPERVISORS (Alameda County) Information
    - CONVENTION AGENDA AMENDMENT
    - FREE SPEECH SONGBOOK. Introduction by Lee Felsenstein. 10 leaves. [ca 1964]
    - GENERAL POLICY STATEMENT OF MILITARY AND POLICE WORKSHOP
    - GUIDELINES FOR CAMPAIGNS
    - Hall (Gus) TOWARD A PEACE TICKET IN 1968. NY: New Outlook, 1967. 30pp.
    - Kahn (Albert E.) TREASON IN CONGRESS. NY: Prog. Citizens of Ame. (1948), 31pp.
    - LABOR WORKSHOP STATEMENTS OF PURPOSE
    - Los Angeles County Delegation (org) EMERGENCY
    - McCARTHY FOR PRESIDENT. Single sheet folded = 8pp.
    - PEACE AND FREEDOM MOVEMENT (blue stock)
    - PEACE AND FREEDOM MOVEMENT. District 4: Supervisorial Office
    - PEACE AND FREEDOM WORKSHOP ON CULTURE
    - Purnell (Eugene) PEACE AND FREEDOM PLATFORM PROPOSAL
    - SPECIFIC PROPOSALSNAT. ORG. / NATIONAL ORGANIZING WORKSHOP
    - SUPPORT THE STRIKE!. Radical Student Union. (= r.s.u.) [Berkeley]
    - Winston (Harry) NEGRO-WHITE UNITY. NY: New Outlook (Feb 1967), 31pp.
  - File 4 (Box 1, Folder 6-8)
    - 11/13/64 memo from Henry May
    - 3/3/65 AE Hutson/ Academic Senate 3pp meeting notice
    - 3/1/65 Academic Senate, Emergency Executive Committee 5 pp 2 cc
    - 3/2/65 Academic Senate, Emergency Executive Committee 11pp
    - 3/10/65 Academic Senate, Emergency Executive Committee
    - 10/28/64 Free Speech Movement Steering Committee
    - 3/5/78 UCB Faculty Members. Press release
    - 3/3/ Revolutionary Communist Youth Brigade
    - 11/30/77 Fund / Open Info. & Accountability = letter / statement of purpose
    - 5/6/65 The Faculty Forum 6 pp
    - 5/24/65 Academic Senate Select Committee on Education 7 pp
    - 5/27/65 Academic Senate Berkeley Division 2 pp
    - 5/25/65 Academic Senate Berkeley Division
    - 12/8/64 UCB Faculty Members
    - 12/4/64 Henry May, Dept. of History
    - 12/3/64 Henry May, Dept. of History
    - 12/3/64 Henry Nash Smith; Richard Harr
    - 12/8/64 Committee on Academic Freedom 5 pp
    - 12/2/64 Academic Senate Berkeley Division 2 pp
    - Friday, nd Free Speech Movement Defense / rally
    - Nd Some ideas for changesFree University 23 half-sheets, stapled
    - Nd Board of Regents [names + addresses]
    - 12/8/64 [petition] to UC Regents 2 cc
    - 12/9/64 Ralph Gleason article, photocopy from SF Chron
    - nd Arthur Hoppe article, photocopy from SF Chron
    - 12/16/64 Free Speech Movement benefit 3 cc
    - 12/17/64 University Students for Law and Order = U.S.L.O. 3 cc
    - Dec. 1964 KPFA
    - 12/17/64 Students for a Democratic Society = SDS
    - 12/15/64 Free Speech Movement Farmer speech poster
    - 6/13/93 SF Examiner Image magazine, letters re Free Speech Movement
    - 5/23/69 Academic Senate Berkeley Division 7 pp
    - 5/23&27/69 Academic Senate Berkeley Division Minutes
    - 6/14/69 Peoples Park Fund
    - 6/9/69 Committee on Student Conduct
    - 6/28/69 Captive Nations Committee of N. Calif.
    - 6/27/69 Berkeley Faculty to Stop the War
    - nd Institute for Historical Review (invit. To subscribe)
    - 4/2/68 Campus Friends of Stop the Draft Week
    - 4/10/68 Campus Friends of Stop the Draft Week
    - 4/26/68 Campus Mobilization Committee
    - 10/13-17/65 Campus Stop the Draft Week
    - nd Independent Socialist Club
    - nd Peoples Voice
    - nd April 27 Mobilization Committee
    - 1/30/68 Raphael Sealey
    - 10/24/67 American Profs for Peace in the Middle East (repr. From NYT)
    - 8/31/67 The Resistance
    - 4/2/68 Joe Esherick & other faculty
    - 3/3/69 ASUC / Center for Participant Education
    - 2/26/69 ASUC / Center for Participant Education
    - 3/23/67 US Dist. Ct. / So. Dist. Ind. ( Funds for Farmers) =GR-FFF 6 pp
    - 7/30/66 GR-FFF 16 pp
    - nd National Farmers Organization = NFO
    - 3/19/67 NFO / GRFFF
    - 3/4/69 Univ. Fed. Teachers / AFT Local 1474 = Berkeley Faculty Union
    - Summer 67 UC Office of the Registrar
    - Nd Negotiation Now!
    - 10/67 Campus SDS Anti-Draft Union
    - 9/7/67 Negotiation Now!
    - 11/7/67 UC Academic Senate Berkeley Div. Minutes
    - 4/16/69 Come to the Regents Meeting demonstration
    - 4/16/69 Union Candidates for Academic Senate
    - 3/12/69 UC Academic Senate
    - nd Berkeley Faculty Union
    - 4/1/69 Campus Community for Ilona Hancock
    - 3/17/69 UC Policies relating to students and student organizations
    - 3/11/69 Union Party report
    - 3/17/69 Oakland 7
    - 3/14/69 Oakland 7
    - 3/13/69 Oakland 7
    - 3/11/69 SDS
    - 3/11/69 Radical Student Union, Labor Committee
    - 3/11/69 Chinese Students Club
    - 3/12/69 TWLF & AFT
    - 3/3/69 Richard Buxbaum, Faculty of Law
    - 3/13/69 Radical Student Union
    - 3/13/69 G.I. Association
    - 4/1/69 GI student action committee
    - 4/2/69 GI-Civilian March
    - 3/31/69 University Bulletin
    - 4/1/69 Socialist Party / Norman Thomas Chapter
    - 4/1/69 One-to-one
  - File 5 (Box 1, Folder 9-11)
    - Bay Area Solidarity Support Campaign. Solidarity Bulletin Number 2 (June)
    - Berkeley Faculty Union. Executive Committee. THE COMMON SENSE OF FACULTY POWER. 11pp. [1969].
    - Berkeley Graduate Nov 1994
    - Berkeley Students For Peace. DISORIENTATION FALL 81. {June] 1982.. Cover by Newman.
    - Berkeley Students For Peace. DISORIENTATION FALL 82. June 15, 1982.
    - Berkshire Conference of Women Historians. [Brief], March 20, 1989. 40pp.
    - Center for Educational Change. April 30, 1969. James Clardy cartoons.. Berkeley Academic Plan Revealed. (16) pp.
    - GDR Committee for Human Rights. Bulletin. #2. 1980. Berlin.
    - Historical Notes, Vol 1:1. (March 9, 1882). Hilgard to Tracy.
    - Mark (Hans) COLD WAR AND THE UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA. Sept, 28, 2001
    - New Mobilization Membership Committee.. Nov. 15 MARCHFall Offensive Against the War. Yellow slip.
    - New Party News 5:3 (Fall 1996)
    - Scheiber (Harry N.) THE IMPACT OF TECHNOLOGY ON AMERCAN LEGAL DEVELOPMENT 1790-1985. A separate transcription from book, [pp. 83-] 125. Inscribed to Leon Litwack.
    - UC, Academic Senate. Minutes. June 2, 1969.
    - UC, Academic Senate. Minutes. Nov. 17, 1969.
    - UC, Academic Senate. Minutes. Nov. 26, 1969.
    - UC, Academic Senate. Minutes. Oct 14, 1969.